## Savanna Baxter

Email: <a href="mailto:srosebaxter@gmail.com">srosebaxter@gmail.com</a> Cell: 704-634-9865 Address: Mooresville, NC, 28117 Website: <a href="mailto:srbaxter.github.io">srbaxter.github.io</a> LinkedIn: <a href="mailto:savannabaxter">savannabaxter</a> GitHub: <a href="mailto:srbaxter">srbaxter</a> Twitter: <a href="mailto:srosebaxter">srosebaxter</a>

### **Summary**

Recent honors graduate with a B.S. in Computer Science from North Carolina State University with experience developing web applications and websites. One year of extensive internship and project experience both personally and with a well-known company. Seeking further opportunities to leverage front-end skills in a collaborative environment.

#### **Education**

May 2016 **North Carolina State University** 

Raleigh, NC

- B.S. in Computer Science, Minor in Music
- 3.667 Cumulative GPA and 3.441 Major GPA

## **Skills**

Languages: HTML5, CSS3, Bootstrap, JavaScript, Python, Java, C
Technologies: Git, GitHub, AWS, Eclipse/IntelliJ, Jenkins, MS Office
Personal: Excellent written and verbal communication, team collaboration
Miscellaneous: Music theory and performance, computer music composition

### **Experience**

NC State Senior Design Project, Raleigh, NC

January - May 2016

SAS: Dynamic IT Dashboard

- Transformed a static, hard-coded, network monitoring dashboard into an interactive one hosted in AWS
- Used D3.js, JavaScript, and HTML5 to generate donut charts to display alerts

SAS Institute Inc., Cary, NC

May - August 2015

Business Intelligence Research & Development Intern

- Modified an existing JavaScript Dependency Analyzer (JDA) back-end Python tool
- Translated the JDA into a RESTful OpenUI5 web application using Flask and jQuery

## **Leadership and Honors**

#### **Women in Computer Science (WiCS)**

Fall 2012 - Spring 2016

President, Ambassador, & Mentor

- Organized rooms, sponsors, and other details to host DiamondHacks
- Officiated officer meetings and 1-2 professional and social events each month
- Served as a Mentor for three younger computer science students

# **Professional Engineering Sorority - Alpha Omega Epsilon** *EOS Committee Co-Chair*

Spring 2013 - 2016

- Acted as Webmaster for three semesters to rebuild our website, Facebook, and Twitter pages *Professional Development Committee Co-Chair* 
  - Served as PD Chair for one semester to instruct Sisters in proper career etiquette
  - Held events about Robert's Rules of Order, graduate school, and job interviews

#### **University Scholars Program**

Fall 2012 - Spring 2016

**Power Sound of the South Marching Band** 

Fall 2012 - 2015

Women in Science and Engineering (WISE)

Fall 2012 - Spring 2014

Ambassador

- Led five tours of Lee Hall while answering questions about WISE and NC State